[Music]
Our special guest is
Ashish Maheshwari ji, many thanks, congratulations, you are very
welcome,
and especially, you are joining this program for the first
time. You accepted our invitation.
Thank you very much Sir.
Certainly, not only will we
learn many things from you that we will be seeing today, but
I feel that it is a very long time since I got the
opportunity to do a program with you, so
thank you very much. The
market seems to be stuck in a dire situation,
but this time it seems that the market is
not ready to go down. What should we expect that
it will be able to cross the barrier of 17817 11700
or do you
think that there are so many concerns at the micro level
that the market cannot go up even after going up.
We are seeing that the complaints that have been coming up are still
not completely resolved. Apart from this, there is a
crisis regarding the bus rates as well, so how are you seeing it?
After the 9-day market, we also saw a 9-day bull run
and now for two days and today is the third day
when the market has fallen.  We are also seeing this from a distance, so
one of the biggest reasons is
that investors who used to make long term investments have
converted a little more into the trading community, a lot of
traders
book their profits very quickly because no one
wants to keep positions overnight for too long
or expect a
huge capital appreciation by taking delivery, so
we are also seeing that the
participation in the volume of the stock exchange has
reduced a little in the cash market of the world by retail, there is
definitely some
support from them and they are again
buying at ₹1000, but still there is
not much pressure, thirdly,
block deals keep happening in many stocks, due to which a
lot of liquidity gets removed
from the market, so my belief is that the
market which
we are seeing trading in a certain territory right now, it will continue to
trade in the same territory in the future also
because as you have seen the
interest rates, there is still no good result in that market.  If they are
not coming then that
is an understanding of it and
apart from this there are monsoon related factors,
I think that in this market
because of the big caps, midcaps, small caps
where there is an individual stock specific story,
they will perform better
in the coming two-three minutes so that the indices of
broad indices, I think they will trade in an orange
and there are many other things too, we will discuss them with you
and at the same time
we have to discuss with you about the big IT companies,
but first of all if you
tell the viewers that if they want to join us
and they have any question regarding the market, then
they can also connect with us on
9311218 74 this is our WhatsApp number through
which you can send us your question,
but yes, whatever question you send, it will be
better if you send it in a little detail, how many shares have you bought, at
what price, what is
your view, for how long can you hold,
if you
send your question or your portfolio with all these details, then it will be helpful
in judging it.  It will be
easy for our experts to review it and
they will also be
able to answer your questions in equal detail. So, in the
meantime, my question was
Sir, regarding the IT market, there was a
boom which was seen for eight to nine days
and the break in it was seen
coming from the IT sector and
we saw Infosys lose 15% votes in a day, this also happens in many years
that such a big giant
company saw such a decline in a day, what are
you thinking about the future of IT companies right now, will we
see more pressure here, should we
buy selected IT stocks right now
because a lot of collection has already been made from the higher level, should we maintain
distance from IT companies right now, are
you suggesting the streets at this time,
right, it is not like that in IT that the
performance has suddenly increased, if you look at the entire track record of one week,
one month, three months, six months, one
year, then the
IT Nifty index has performed very well, in fact,
if you look at the product market from a high of 33000  The 18
digitization has reached the level of 26800,
so the IT index is probably standing near its 52 week low of around 26200, so the
reason behind it is that the
big cap and IT companies have been
performing inside, we have to understand that
because you used to
give high valuations to these IT companies because their
growth has been very significant
and if you are going for quarter over quarter 3%-4% growth
or are
going for the wrong thing with the fierce, then why will
they get a multiple of 30 times or 40 times.
Secondly, because
in that market also we have seen a lot of pressure on IT stocks,
so if there has to be a buying, then
first of all
stocks like Apple, Microsoft, Google will be bought,
not project stocks like Infosys, TCS.
So my advice would be to
avoid the big cap stocks
and where mid cap IT stocks have their own
individual story, there
opportunities should be sought for banking, so I think here
Persistence system as soon as a company or a
company like a capital reserves a lot of merit,
not a large capital, I
think the entire quarter will perform well, there will be
pressure in a way, this is what
Maheshwari
ji believes, but amidst all this, many people are
joining us through YouTube and WhatsApp,
asking their questions, Rahul Dravid ji is saying,
good afternoon, very good afternoon
Rahul ji, and it is a good thing that you
join the program every day and
interact with us, Ranjit Bhatia ji is
asking that if one wants to
invest in IDFC Limited for the long term, then at
what levels should one enter and
how do you see the future here,
so Ashish ji, I would like to know your opinion on IDFC Limited,
right now it is trading around ₹80,
Ashish, around 67 and it is
interesting to know that investing for the long term is looking
good for you, HDFC Limited, in
fact, IDFC Limited and IDFC
First Bank, both are good stocks and
both have made a lot of gains.  The performance
of both is quite good in comparison to other banking stocks that have performed well. I am fully
confident that whenever the results of both
come, we are expecting very good results here.
And in terms of Certificate Bill B
and stocks, my advice would be that
both IDFC First Bank and IDFC should be
on your buying list.
If you want to see the levels, I think
you can definitely enter at a level around 78.
Sir, we
saw a good rally in IRCTC Railway stock yesterday
and a lot of
questions started coming in from the viewers, including those who had
invested in IRCTC at higher levels
and also from those who were watching whether the
collective momentum that was built in RVNL or other Railtels should be played.
We see that in Railway stock, after the
budget, a momentum is
visible. What are your big thoughts on the reason for this momentum yesterday?
And secondly, will
this current trend in Railway stocks sustain for a few days?
Look, there is a huge basket on Railway stock as well.  Right now,
companies are
working in the railway sector and in fact, the best
performing stock is
IRCTC. I would not recommend investing
in IRCTC right now because
I think the
quality we have seen from the financial side and in which
even at the level above 900, the retailer has always been quite
trapped, so as the stock
increases, there is more supply in it as
compared to the demand, the reason for this I think
that stocks like IBN or Titagarh Wagon Limited,
which are direct play, the fundamentals
of the companies are also good and
we have seen a good improvement in their performance, their Kautilya numbers, one should invest
in these stocks, I would advise to avoid
stocks like IRCTC RFC right now, so I would
advise to avoid these stocks.
Meanwhile, there are some news areas in
which we saw that the Root of License has
touched its 52-week high today
and here they have received USFDA approval for a medicine.
Now,
Sir, regarding the overall pharma sector, what
trend is visible here and
we  It was seen that after the rally seen during the time of Covid, the
pharma sector has seen consistent underperformance
but again some momentum
seems to be waning. But amidst all this,
Life Sciences is completely
outperforming and today
it has made its new 52 week high. So, are
you seeing any positivity here right now? Are you thinking
that this momentum will be
seen to be waning or are you thinking that the
momentum was built due to the news and now
perhaps some cold water will be seen here.
Life Sciences is a very strong company. The
company has been consistently making profits of more than Rs 500 crore on
quarterly wages
and my belief is that wherever there are performing
stocks, the demand is the same. So, there is
good demand from institutions in Live Sense.
Apart from this, we have seen a very
good
rally in Glenmark, so Sun Pharma is at
number three. Apart from that, Disease Doctor
Ready, all the stocks have
already started performing well after finding their bottom
and have gone down.  It is not that the
domestic market is seeing a bounce back,
so after the comment, the call
off period was done and now the valuations in the stock have become
so attractive,
so you are getting the benefit of that, your
funds want to go towards a little different sector.
Secondly,
what has happened in these companies in the last 2 years, sir, whether the company is
in tea and world trade or
formulations, they have done a
lot of expansion, the
outcome of which will now start coming from this financial
and due to this
region, you are seeing that appetite is being created
again in the chemical sector in the farmer sector,
so I believe that
stocks like Gland Pharma should
also be kept under watch here and in fact, they are
quite good and since
we are currently talking about pharma,
we are seeing that today a good
rise is being seen in Piramal Pharma also, a
rise of more than 9% is being
seen here, once again staying around 7879.  The
momentum
seems to be waning but in the meantime
Darshan has sent his question to our Darshan
and right now we are trying to contact him but
perhaps he is not picking up the phone. I brought
his question because
he has WhatsApped us so let's
discuss his question and his question
here is Anant Trivedi ji from Kota Rajasthan
and his question is that I have
bought 14 shares of Muthoot at the price of ₹38,
although he has said that I
bought it for short term but now
since it is incurring loss so it is still here,
now it should be known that it means
it is making profit, is it saying that
you should book profit at this time or should I stay in
it, so
sir I would like to know your opinion on Muthoot, it has been bought for ₹938, it is
trading around ₹1047 now,
at ₹100 it is making
profit around Rs.100, although
whatever he had bought was for short term
but now he is making good profit, that is
why he is confused  Should we
book profits once or is there still a possibility of further upside? There is a possibility
that we should book profits right now at a stable level
because this stock has also made its high of 1300
and is now consolidating a bit and
we are seeing a little pressure in the Gold Finance Company,
so you will see
that whether it is Param or
Kabhi Nehru, they are trading in the range, so
I would advise you. I recommend two other stocks on this page.
My
Fincorp looks quite attractive to me at this level.
Apart from this, you can
also enter the stock of Piramal Enterprises at this level.
You will get a good
return here. Compare that, you can book a lot of profit.
You can buy in Enterprises.
And secondly, which one did
you mention, which one will
I
make for you? And when we bid farewell
to Maheshwari ji, you will be
reminded once again in this section, but in the
meantime, Shailendra Suman ji has
connected with us through YouTube and is asking questions,
and he has done it properly.  A
list of three-four stocks has been sent to us. Firstly,
we will come in NMDC Steel Metal and
because today there has been a lot of longs in metals and
after that a little momentum has been
seen, he has bought 500
shares of NMDC at the price of 73,
he has bought Renuka Sugar, 1000 shares
at the price of 55 rupees, he has bought a fertilizer company,
he has bought
300 shares at 330 rupees and I want to know
whether this portfolio of his which has been
made of three companies is correct and
how should any of these be kept in future, what
kind of targets can be seen,
so NMDC Sugar Company, Renuka Sugar,
apart from this he has bought shares of Fact Fertilizer,
how were you looking at the companies,
see, I am not very bullish on NMDC Steel right now, I am
not convinced
that right now the big cap steel stocks are facing
some problems in moving,
so it may take a lot of time to come in midcap steel, so
if you want to stay in the market then
I would suggest you to
invest in Vedanta because there  You
also get tractor dividend almost every quarter
and there is a
lot of stability in the price from time to time. So
can Vedanta buy more from NMDC?
Regarding Renu Sugar, this stock is also
trapped at a very high level, due to which
it is
not getting any momentum in the stock and whenever there is a
slight increase in the stock, we
see that the ceiling is here, so a little bit.
But still I would
advise you to wait. My opinion is that
after looking at the things inside the cotton, you can buy it tomorrow.
However, if the level of 48-50 will be
a good level for exit. The third
stock is your fertilizer chemical, this is a
very good company in your portfolio
and if you have bought it at 330 right now, then hold on to that
stock. The target of this stock will be
between 360 to 30090 after the scouter numbers come because both
fertilizer and chemical portfolio have very good results
and this quarter is a very good relief.  Regarding
their company, we hope
Shailendra ji, you must have got the answer to your question
and you must have understood what needs to be done.
If we stay out of DC for now
and do something on behalf of Medanta, then
you will get better returns there.
Rahul Dravid ji has asked a question about
them. He has bought 50 shares
of Barbecue and he bought these at the
price of 768 for the long term. He is saying that
my view is what should I do now.
We saw the shares falling from around ₹1200 and it
went up to 624, although they did
not buy them at a very high price. They bought them at 768
and now we will see, the price is running at 627, so it is still
much below their buying price. If you have a
long term view, then should we continue
or do you think that
whatever was being said in this sector has ended. We should maintain
some distance.
See, whatever was being said about the sector,
we got to see it when the reopening happened after Covid, so right now the
stock is at
12500.  The level was touched and since then a
lot of selling was seen because the
numbers are not very good, the
ratio of 12th is such that this market cap does
not deserve it, so
we have seen a lot of selling off from the institutional players here.
I am sure you have to stay in the food sector,
so I would advise you to
buy Varun Beverages. I believe this stock has a
market cap of around Rs 1 lakh crore at this level,
but because Pepsi has a proxy play
and as the heat is going to be the hottest, you
will see that the beverage stocks are going to do well,
so if you invest in Varun Beverages,
it will give you butter returns.
You are incurring a loss of Rs 100-100 from here,
Rahul ji. And if you want,
invest in Varun Beverages. You are also seeing the weather, the
heat is continuously
increasing rapidly, especially in the North,
you will see the benefit of that here in Varun Beverages.
Meanwhile,
before moving on to the next Darshan, Sir, I would like to understand from you the
results of ICC Lombard.
We saw that the results of Prime Efficiency looked
good but there are a lot of concerns
here regarding which
we are seeing that today a big ground is being seen.
If you have seen the results of you and ICC Lombard, then
how are you seeing it?
In the coming time, there are a lot of concerns regarding this entire sector,
especially
regarding the insurance sector. And in the budget,
efforts are being made in this way that people should
not go in this direction to save tax. Then
you feel that some future
of these companies is in the base, due to this reason, this
ground is being seen. The
close is only ₹30-₹40. The stock has moved away,
so there was already a lot of ceiling pressure in this stock. The
second thing is that the
portfolio mix is ​​changing because
one of their four competencies was auto
insurance and not health insurance.
What is happening now, the vertical of health insurance is seeing a
good pick up, but since last
time, the auto vertical is losing from the market. So
this is the thing that is
not being understood about this trick that why while
Auto sales are increasing so much, almost 40
lakh vehicles are being sold every year,
after that all their renewals take place, after that
you have such a superior franchise,
ICC Bank has such a big network, it has such a
big network of its own, still
your hold in this segment is decreasing, so this is
one reason, apart from this the valuation is
already quite rich, the
market cap is almost 52-53 thousand crores right now, so
in comparison to the peer set I think it is quite
aggressive, so there was a
little collection given in this stock and that is happening
and I think this stock will
not fall further, it is okay, there will be
more ground in the counter also on this ground, so if after the result you are
thinking that now the ground has gained enough,
you should enter, then
this kind of advice is definitely not from Ashish ji,
meanwhile Gurmeet Singh ji has joined
and is saying very good afternoon very good
afternoon Gurmeet ji and it is a good thing that
you are asking your question, what are you saying about
my  Infosys is at a rate of 1555. I had
taken it for 5 years. Can we average Infosys now
Sir, this is a very common question
which is being asked continuously by the audience
that whether all the analysts of IT giants like Infosys,
TCS, Wipro have
always been saying positive things, so even those who
have it at higher prices are also
thinking that things will get better in 2-4-6 months,
so most of the people are
asking questions about everything, in this scenario, in the
current gold, when there is talk of recession, there is talk of
layoffs in IT companies, should everything be done
in such a time
or should a loss be booked for one time, for those who have become
fans at a high level,
what will be your opinion on Infospace,
especially for those who have already taken shares, see the
future prospects of Infosys,
I feel that companies which are only
in the software services business or big
banks or in bus sectors where there is
more exposure, there is
more problem, even then look at Infosys  If
we look at it, the exposure in the BF segment is more than TCS, if more than 30% of the revenue comes from there, its holding is quite high here, then almost 36% will be broken here from the fish side, so you will see that whenever bad numbers
come, we have seen a big reaction from their side here,
and it has
also come in cotton, so now what happens is that
after the sell-off that happened on Monday, there are a lot of domestic
investors, who did not buy the stock,
retail traders and investors got involved in this stock
thinking it to be a value wine, so due to which
I think the
pressure on this stock will continue, if you were to do an
average of Infosys, then my mother is the weight of 52 week low,
if you think, I think the
level will be around Rs 11:30, so the
earnings there are exactly because at that
time the stock will be trading at 17 times, due to
25 warning, so we are advising our clients to
wait a little more, but there will be streets, so let's
hope.  You must have got the answer to your question,
meanwhile Shivam Mittal ji is saying
that I have
DSL at the price of 800, Map Me
India at the price of 1200 and
Girl File at the price of ₹600.  All
three companies are good but the prices are not rising.
My view is for a very long term, whether it is
good or bad, only the experts will
tell. Shivam ji, we ask
Maheshwari ji once that if he tracks
these companies, he has bought two DSLs at a
price of 800, Sir Map Me India at a
price of 1200 and the shares of Gulf oil at a
price of ₹600. Now he believes
that all three companies are good but the prices
are not rising. However, the entire market is
not where there is much rising. How should you do it
because he is saying
that the view is very long or you should
switch these stocks.
My advice would be to switch from all three stocks.
I think that yes, the stocks have reached a slightly higher
valuation, but if you want to
recover in the short term, then you will have to
withdraw from the stock and
move to some other stock. Jain, after
selling DSL, my advice would be that you
invest in MCX stock or Angel One stock
where it is its proxy play
and Butterworth you should take it seriously.  You
can give these two stocks in comparison. I
also advise you to sell your India. I think
that the euphoria of IPO is over once
and because of this, if you
invest in any auto stock, then here
I would advise you to invest in JBM Auto stock
and if you look at the factor company from such a girl file, then there is a
company by the name of Panama Petroleum Limited which is
debt free and quite good.
In the last two years, we have seen
Panama Petrol Pump coming from there.
So I hope you have got the answer to your question. Get
out of these three companies and it will be
better if you invest in the three new companies that have been mentioned. In the meantime, another
special guest has joined us. Let's introduce him once.
Santosh Singh ji has
now joined the program and
he will be a
part of our program from 1:30 to 2:00. So Santosh
ji, thank you very much and congratulate you for
joining this program, but before leaving,
I have one last question, since we have 1 minute
time, I have a child.  I would like to
discuss with Maheshwari ji the
questions that have come in and Maheshwari ji, one of our
Darshan Suman ji has sent a question, he
wants to know your opinion on JEL,
he has bought JEL shares and his
purchase has been a little higher, say his
purchase is above 200, what should I do now, should I stay
or should I exit
JEL, you should see, for years
only performance has been seen and the
pricing formula and
even after all these issues, we have
not seen any improvement in the stock, so I think if
you want to be in the gas sector then there can be
no better thing than Mangal IGL
because the pricing
formula of gas will get the biggest benefit of revision, it is
almost debt free company, they have a
lot of cash flow, they also have free cash flow, so
in both these stocks, you can shift
sir, in the end, apart from the recommendations that you have given, would you
like to recommend something else to
our viewers, so
what is the history, I would like to share it with your viewers,
first my pick will be
and the reason is that last year the company's  It was
working, the company had made a loss of about 9 crores,
this year the profit increased to about 65 to
70 crores, if you want then at a
market cap of 1300 crores you are getting a company earning ₹70 crores, so that is why
I have seen a lot of
value and because this time the summer is
very extreme, so the demand for beer is going to
increase a lot, the second stock which I like is a
thousand crores market cap company,
Atul Auto Limited of the automobile sector,
keep a close eye on this stock as well,
last year the company earned ₹22000 brother, you are selling a
vehicle in front of the child tomorrow and
this year it is about 32000 brother, tomorrow the
company will be saved, then 32000 brother, tomorrow the
company that will sell is my mother,
this time their profit will be about 3 crores, so the loss of
history is 25 crores, so that is positive
and in this market cap it is difficult to find an Ave maker
and a CNG and a three wheeler
company, so it should be
kept in close view and there is a good boom
in Sohan Distance  We are seeing a
rise of around 6.5% while trading intraday. The sound resistance is
around 170. If you could show our viewers the chart of
Somesh's intraday and the same if there is a
little pressure in Atul Limited,
but Atul Auto said Sir,
if we take a look at the
situation here, then here also
if we see, we can see a rise of around 2.5%.
Rohit Sher is
moving in good momentum. Maheshwari Sir, thank you
very much. We
hope that
you will continue to share your knowledge with our viewers
and will remain associated with our program.
And thank you very much.
No discriminatory words from your side.
[Music]
First of all, you have given advice to your viewers.
We are also commenting on this stock. So,
you may find the stock in all their portfolios.
Thank you very much Sir for
giving your valuable time to join today's discussion.
[Music]